shopgate.com 2019-06-03

# Privacy Policy | Shopgate

The Shopgate privacy policy

### Privacy Policy

1) Shopgate Inc., based in 2222 Rio Grande Street, Suite 300, Austin, TX 78741 (subsequently “Shopgate” or “Provider”), uses the personal data of Buyers or Merchants (e.g. title, name, address, e-mail address, phone number, fax number, bank details) according to the regulations of the American data protection law.

(2) The personal data of a Buyer or Merchant are used exclusively for the handling of the concluded contracts between the parties, for instance for billing purposes. Sole exceptions are newsletters or emails, regarding offers of Shopgate or Merchants of Shopgate, which can be unsubscribed at any time.

(3) All personal data of Buyers or Merchants that have been transmitted to Shopgate will not be accessible to third parties without a written consent from the Buyer or the Merchant. This may not apply in case of a legal or official investigation.

(4) Shopgate uses Cookies on several pages to make the visit on our website or on our applications appealing and to enable the use of certain functions. The Cookies are small text files, which will be stored on your computer. Most of the Cookies that we use will be deleted from your hard drive when the browser session finishes (so-called Session-Cookies). Other Cookies stay on the computer and allow us to recognize your computer the next time you visit us (so-called long-term-Cookies). These Cookies serve to welcome you with your username. They also save time to the Buyer and the Merchant in case of subsequent orders. The generated Cookies will last a few months. It is not allowed for the Merchants connected to Shopgate to collect, process or use the personal data via Cookies through our website.

(5) A free support service is available under the e-mail address support@shopgate.com, if other information is sought after or if the deletion of the Buyer’s or Merchant’s data is desired.

(6) Data for marketing and improvement purposes shall be collected and saved on this website and on the mobile trading platforms of Shopgate. From this data user profiles with a pseudonym will be created. Cookies may be used for this as well. The collected data shall not be used to identify the visitor of this website personally and shall not be united with personal data through the carrier of the pseudonym without a consent given specifically by the person concerned.  
When you visit our website some information (commonly known as a “cookie”) may be stored on your computer. Cookies are text files which a website transfers to your hard drive to store and sometimes track information about you. Cookies are specific to the server that created them and cannot be accessed by other servers, which means that they cannot be used to track your movements around the web. Passwords and credit card numbers are not stored in cookies.  
A cookie helps you get the best out of the website and helps us to provide you with a more customized service. We use cookies for the following purposes:

So that you will not have to re-enter your details each time you visit the website, and to track how our site is used and to improve and update the content of the website.

You can accept or refuse cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser’s settings to refuse them if you wish. Certain parts of the website are reliant on the use of cookies to operate correctly and may not work correctly if you set your browser not to accept cookies.
